

# **NGUYEN VAN A**

# **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and eriam eaque ipsa, quae ab illo inven of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

### **EDUCATION**



### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. inciple of selection: he rejects plea administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

#### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. corporate administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

# **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

#### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult rum. 5 PARAGRAPHS COPY DISCOVER MORE! Check out our new font g and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

## Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to runt mollitia an goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

#### Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute

# **ACTIVITIES**



Sep 2003 - 2007

#### **CVPRO JSC**

#### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer n the 1960s with the release of Letraset' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

# **CERTIFICATIONS**



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2004

# HONORS & AWARDS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2013 - 2014

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US Rackham "But I must explain to you how all this mistaken idea of denouncing pleasure and pra

#### **REFERENCES**



### **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

### **SKILLS**



Words Photoshop

Excel English

Power Point Japanese

### **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt vẫn không hề bị thay đổi. Nó đã được phổ biến trong những năm 1960 nhờ việc bán những and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities